Finding Aid for Clarence T. Johnston Papers, 1888-1941
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Camp Davis Summer Surveying Camp Photos 1911-1928
  - 1911 Session
    - Camp Davis and Biological Station, looking along the shore of South Fishtail Bay (Box 9:5)
    - Looking NE across South Fishtail Bay from the ridge to the W of camp (Box 9:5)
    - Region W of Big Springs after fire (Box 9:5)
    - Possible campsite, near Butler's on Burt Lake, 3 plates (Box 9:5)
      [8-10]
    - Douglas Lake from tower at NE Base. This view, with numbers 12, 13, and 14 forms a panorama of the lake, 4 plates (Box 9:5)
      [11-14]
    - North shore of Burt Lake (Box 9:5)
  - 1912 Session
    - Lumber shed. This is 12 x 16 ft. measured on the floor and 7 1/2 ft. high. It is used for storing the best of the cement, lime, and boats (Box 9:5)
    - Concrete storehouse. View from the rear. This is 15 x 30 ft. and 7 1/2 to 8 ft. high. The roof is concrete (Box 9:5)
    - View of western part of camp, looking NW from hill behind camp (Box 9:5)
    - View of eastern part of camp, looking NE from behind camp (4] (Box 9:5)
    - Douglas Lake, looking north from hill behind camp (Box 9:5)
    - Camp group (6] (Box 9:5)
    - The swimming period (Box 9:5)
    - Carpenter shop (Box 9:5)
    - Grapevine Point (Box 9:5)
    - Region west of Big Springs after fire (Box 9:5)
    - Possible campsite, near Butler's on Burt Lake (Box 9:5)
      [11]
    - Inspection trip around burnt-over region after fire (Box 9:5)
    - View along new trail to Burt Lake (Box 9:5)
    - Possible campsite, near Butler's (Box 9:5)
    - On Colonial Point, Burt Lake (Box 9:5)
    - Possible campsite, near Butler's (Box 9:5)
    - View along new trail to Burt Lake (Box 9:5)
      [17]
    - Tower at SW Base (Box 9:5)
    - The Office Tent (Box 9:5)
      [19]
    - The swimming period, 2 plates (Box 9:5)
      [20-21]
    - Looking westerly along the shore in front of camp (Box 9:5)
    - Burned hotel on Colonial Point, Burt Lake (Box 9:5)
      [23]
    - Possible campsite, near Butler's on Burt Lake, 2 plates (Box 9:5)
      [24-25]
    - Camp Davis looking E along the shore of South Fishtail Bay (Box 9:5)
      [26]
    - Solar work, set up on the camp meridian (Box 9:5)
      [27]
    - Camp Davis, looking W along the shore of Douglas Lake (Box 9:5)
    - Engineer's mess tent, 2 plates (Box 9:5)
      [36-37]
    - Camp Davis from the west (Box 9:5)
    - Poll call (Box 9:5)
    - The base line (Box 9:5)
      [41]
    - Interior of store house built in 1912. The ceiling is composed of cedar poles supporting the concrete roof. The view was taken before the concrete floor was placed (Box 9:5)
      [43]
    - New concrete store house (Box 9:5)
      [44]
    - Camp groups, 5 plates (Box 9:5)
      [45, 47-50]
    - Harbor built during the summer of 1912. The entrance to the harbor is shown near the two poppel trees on the right. The basin is 28 x 60 ft. (Box 9:5)
      [51]
    - Method of protecting boats prior to 1912 (Box 9:5)
      [52]
  - 1913 Session
    - View of camp from elevation S of harbor (Box 9:5)
    - State Street, showing an attempt to improve State St. by mixing cedar bark with the sand. This is helpful but not entirely satisfactory. The appearance of the street is not improved, to say the least (Box 9:5)
    - Cement block machine made in camp. This machine molded all of the blocks that entered into the construction of the new store house, built during the summer of 1913. Notice the hinges and looks, all 1/2" galvanized pipe. One of the palates for supporting the block until the cement sets is shown in position in the machine (Box 9:5)
    - Store house. Rear of concrete store house built during the season of 1912. This is 15 x 30 ft. and 7 1/2 to 8 ft. high. The roof is concrete (Box 9:5)
    - Store house. Note the top of the well curbing and the engine for pumping water and running dynamo. The tank in the corner is part of the engine cooling system (Box 9:5)
    - View from the near center of camp, showing concrete floor built during summer of 1912 and piers, for sextant work, made of concrete blocks during summer of 1913 (Box 9:5)
    - Kitchen and mess tents. Tent on right is engineers' mess tent and one on left is biological mess tent (8] (Box 9:5)
    - At Big Springs-Hugh Brodie, C.O. Carey, Prof. H.G. Rashbacher, Prof. H.H. Atwell, Mrs. Davis, Prof. J.B. Davis (Box 9:5)
    - At Big Springs-C.O. Carey, Prof. J.B. Davis, Prof. H.H. Atwell, Hugh Brodie, Prof. C.T. Johnston, Mrs. Davis (Box 9:5)
    - Prof. Johnston's tent (Box 9:5)
    - State St., looking E from near harbor (Box 9:5)
    - Looking S along the shore from Grapeview Point (Box 9:5)
    - N shore of Burt Lake (Box 9:5)
    - Looking down the base line toward NE base (Box 9:5)
      [171]
    - At Big Springs (Box 9:5)
    - Staff, 3 plates (Box 9:5)
      [19-21]
    - Camp groups, 4 plates (Box 9:5)
      [25-28]
    - Store house built during the summer of 1913 similar to that built during 1912 but built of concrete blocks and with a steel roof (Box 9:5)
      [29]
    - Triangulation station off of Grapevine Pt., taken from the Point (Box 9:5)
      [30]
    - At Big Springs-Hugh Brodie, C.O. Carey, Prof. H.H. Atwell, Prof. C.T. Johnston, Mrs. Davis, Prof. J.B. Davis (Box 9:5)
    - Prof. Johnston's tent (Box 9:5)
      [32]
    - Double SW Base (Box 9:5)
    - Carp Creek in the Big Springs region (Box 9:5)
  - 1914 Session
    - Student group pictures, 4 plates (Box 9:5)
      [8-11]
  - 1915 Session
    - Construction of the kitchen. (Box 9:5)
      (View from the SE showing the erection of roof trusses. Taken at about 10 AM, August 18, 1915. The rafters had been framed during the earlier days of the week. They were all in place before noon.)
    - Sidewalk construction, showing framework of kitchen in background. New administration building in middle of picture (Box 9:5)
    - The mess employees (Box 9:5)
    - Construction of the kitchen. (Box 9:5)
      (Taken during the afternoon of August 19, 1915, the building being complete with the exception of hinging the doors and windows and attaching the ridge cap)
    - Grapevine Point (Box 9:5)
    - Teaching staff summer of 1915., 2 plates (Box 9:5)
      (Bottom row 1 to rt) C.O. Wisler, W.M. Cannan, John H. Bringhorst, Howard B. Merrick, John Bonin, Horace W. King, Dr. C.B. Stouffer, Clarence T. Johnston. (Second row 1 to rt) A.N. Laird, C.N. Ward, G.W. Smedberg James H. Cissel, H.C. Smith, G.M. Bleekman. In doorway, W.H. Code, S.B. Douglas
      [23-24]
    - Construction of sanitary system. (Box 9:5)
      (View of the sewer line looking toward the septic tank. This was taken during the early stages of the work and the batter boards first used are shown. Some idea may be had of the brush which had to be cleared and grubbed before any trenching could be done by the brush on both sides of the trench)
    - Sidewalk construction, mixing concrete, 3 plates (Box 9:5)
      [26-28]
    - Construction of the sanitary system. (Box 9:5)
      (View of the completed septic tank, showing the camp and two of the toilets in the distance. The two manholes and the opening under the boards near the middle of the tank give ample opportunity for a thorough inspection at any time)
    - View of western part of camp. (Box 9:5)
      (Taken from the top of the new concrete reservoir constructed to store water for the sanitary system. The new kitchen is in the foreground. An interesting comparison is furnished in the relative appearance of the standard tents and the steel buildings. One of each is shown to the right of the center of the view)
    - State St. looking E along State St. from the west end. (Box 9:5)
      (This photograph was taken about the end of the fourth week of camp and before much had been accomplished by the citizens in the way of a general municipal cleaning. The view gives a splendid idea of the condition of the young trees on the campground E311 Central portion of camp, looking S. This photograph was taken from the top of the diving tower. It shows the location of the new kitchen)
    - Construction of the sanitary sewer. View of the 8" pipe line. Note grade pole and batter boards (Box 9:5)
    - An example of steel construction (Box 9:5)
    - Camp store. This was the second steel building erected in camp (Box 9:5)
    - State St. looking W from E end, a few days before Visitors' Day. (Box 9:5)
      (The neat appearance of the camp is evidence of much hard work having been done. Attention is called to the birch "Welcome to Camp Davis" displayed over the center of the street)
    - North shore of Burt Lake (Box 9:5)
    - On the N shore of Burt Lake. Prof. C.T. Johnston, C.N. Johnston, Prof. H.B. Merrick, F.D. Johnston, John Bonin (Box 9:5)
      [39]
    - Computations in the office tent (Box 9:5)
    - Two at once (Box 9:5)
    - Camp Davis, looking westerly along the shore (Box 9:5)
      [42]
    - A high dive (Box 9:5)
  - 1916 Session
    - Camp Davis and the Biological Station, looking East along the shore of South Fishtail Bay (Box 9:5)
    - Furnish your own title (two divers) (Box 9:5)
    - Burt Lake (Box 9:5)
    - Looking across South Fishtail Bay toward North Fisthtail Say, from Camp Davis (Box 9:5)
    - Looking toward Grapevine Pt. from Camp Davis (Box 9:5)
    - A section of Camp Davis from the diving tower (Box 9:5)
    - Camp Davis from the south ridge of Grapevine Pt. (Box 9:5)
    - Camp Davis from the west shore of South Fishtail Bay (Box 9:5)
    - The camp wireless station and operator, C.N. Johnston (Box 9:5)
    - Framework of new mess tent (Box 9:5)
    - The camp truck (Box 9:5)
    - Part of the staff-Prof. C.T. Johnston, A.R. Bailey, J. Schmutz, Prof. H.H. Atwell, Prof. H.B. Merrick, H. Brodie (Box 9:5)
    - On the new trail down to the mouth of Carp Creek-Prof. C.O. Carey, Prof. Hugh Brodie, Prof. H.H. Atwell, Prof. H.B. Merrick, John Bonin (Box 9:5)
  - 1917 Session
    - Camp group August 10, 1917 Dean Cooley, Prof. Davis and Prof. Hoad visiting camp at the time (Box 9:5)
    - A quiet spot near the mouth of Carp Creek looking upstream from the right bank (Box 9:5)
    - The new launch, boat 18, making a harbor for itself at the mouth of Carp Creek., 2 plates (Box 9:5)
      [4, 6]
      (The work was directed by Prof. H.B. Merrick and he was assisted by teaching assistant George M. Bleekman and the keeper of the Bogardus Tract, Vernon C. Jarman)
    - Camp group August 10, 1917 Dean Cooley, Prof. Davis and Prof. Hoad visiting camp at the time (Box 9:5)
    - Camp group August 10, 1917 Dean Cooley, Prof. Davis and Prof. Hoad visiting camp at the time, 2 plates (Box 9:6)
      [9-10]
    - The new launch, boat 18, making a harbor for itself at the mouth of Carp Creek (Box 9:6)
    - Near the mouth of Carp Creek (Box 9:6)
    - State St. looking W from near E end of camp. New steel buildings on left (Box 9:6)
    - Bringing the launch up from Burt Lake. Hauling it out of the water at Burt Lake (Box 9:6)
    - Bringing the launch up from Burt Lake. Lifting it up onto the carriage, 2 plates (Box 9:6)
    - Bringing the launch up from Burt Lake, 3 plates (Box 9:6)
      [11-13]
    - New steel buildings erected during summer of 1919 (Box 9:6)
    - Road from State St. by kitchen, looking westerly (Box 9:6)
    - Road from State St. by kitchen, looking easterly (Box 9:6)
    - Camp Davis looking NW from hill behind kitchen (Box 9:6)
    - Camp Davis looking NE from hill behind kitchen (Box 9:6)
    - Camp Davis looking W from the shore of South Fishtail Bay (Box 9:6)
    - Camp groups, 4 plates (Box 9:6)
      [23-25, 28]
    - Tractor and wagon hauling gravel (Box 9:6)
    - Prof. Johnston's shack (Box 9:6)
  - 1920 Session
    - State road leading to Cheboygan about 1/4 mile East of camp (Box 9:6)
    - Steel residence building erected in 1914 Camp group. For names see camp report 1920 (Box 9:6)
    - Steps up hill near center of camp replaced 1920 (Box 9:6)
    - Looking down on Burt Lake from the hill behind camp (Box 9:6)
    - Looking over South Fishtail Bay from the hill behind camp, toward Grapevine Point with a glimpse of camp below (Box 9:6)
    - Looking E along proposed new road from center of Section 34 (Box 9:6)
    - Harbor drained for winter, showing wooden shelter built around launch (Box 9:6)
    - State St. looking E from W end of camp (Box 9:6)
    - Looking down toward Burt Lake from the hill back of camp (Box 9:6)
    - Looking over South Fishtail Bay from the hill behind the kitchen, with a glimpse of camp (Box 9:6)
    - The Biological Station is in the background (Box 9:6)
    - Looking down on Burt Lake from the hill back of camp (Box 9:6)
    - Looking over South Fishtail Bay from the hill behind the kitchen, with a glimpse of camp (Box 9:6)
    - Looking across South Fishtail Bay to North Fishtail Bay. Taken from the hill behind camp (Box 9:6)
    - Camp groups, 4 plates (Box 9:6)
      [23-26]
    - Camp groups. See Camp Davis report for names, 2 plates (Box 9:6)
      [37-38]
    - Harbor, showing shelter to house launch during winter (Box 9:6)
    - View of Camp Davis from hill behind kitchen (Box 9:6)
    - Double (Box 9:6)
    - State St. looking W from near center of camp showing new sidewalk (Box 9:6)
    - Area behind administration building, showing instrument building and out-door workshops (Box 9:6)
    - Grading work around the harbor in preparation for the construction of a new harbor next year, 3 plates (Box 9:6)
      [44-46]
    - Part of Camp Davis from the hill behind camp, 2 plates (Box 9:6)
      [47-48]
    - Looking along proposed new road, 2 plates (Box 9:6)
      [49-50]
  - 1921 Session
    - Harbor construction, 2 plates (Box 9:6)
      [1-2]
    - First office building erected and foundation for 2nd building completed (Box 9:6)
    - Harbor Building completed (Box 9:6)
    - Completed office building looking W. Foundation and floor for second office building in foreground (Box 9:6)
    - End of harbor entrance channel showing temporary dam (Box 9:6)
    - Harbor entrance channel (Box 9:6)
    - New harbor building (Box 9:6)
    - Harbor building from the SE, Monday evening September 23, 1921 (Box 9:6)
    - Concrete construction of harbor about August 22, 1921 [10] (Box 9:6)
    - Second camp, September 13, 1921. Visit of Pres. Burton, 2 plates (Box 9:6)
      [12-13]
    - Channel-lake to harbor-looking toward Douglas Lake (Box 9:6)
    - Camp groups 2d session 1921., 2 plates (Box 9:6)
      (See Camp Davis report for names)
    - Staff, 2d session 1921, 2 plates (Box 9:6)
      [26-27]
    - Camp groups 1st session 1921. See Camp Davis report for names, 2 plates (Box 9:6)
      [28-29]
    - Staff, 1st session June 1921, 2 plates (Box 9:6)
  - 1922 Session
    - Camp group, 2d session (Box 9:6)
    - Camp group, 1st session (Box 9:6)
    - Road leading to kitchen (Box 9:6)
    - Camp group, 1st session (Box 9:6)
    - Camp group, 2d session (Box 9:6)
    - Camp group, 1st session, 2 plates (Box 9:6)
      [6-7]
    - Camp group, 2d session (Box 9:6)
    - New ice house, putting sheet steel on west side (Box 9:6)
    - Interior of harbor building (Box 9:6)
    - Librarian W.W. Bishop, Mrs. C.T. Johnston and Franklin Johnston (Box 9:6)
    - Looking easterly from the hill behind camp (Box 9:6)
    - Douglas Lake and a glimpse of Camp Davis from the hill behind camp (Box 9:6)
    - Grapevine Point, looking from the hill behind camp across South Fishtail Bay, with a glimpse of Camp Davis below (Box 9:6)
    - Looking across South Fishtail Bay and a part of camp toward North Fishtail Bay, from the hill behind camp (Box 9:6)
    - Road leaving street to go to kitchen, clay applied to this branch (Box 9:6)
    - State St. looking toward center of camp from near building 22 (Box 9:6)
    - Area graded back of store (Box 9:6)
    - State St. looking toward harbor from near building 22 (Box 9:6)
    - Garage, clay applied to area in front of building (Box 9:6)
    - Center of camp showing effect of clay applied to gravel road (Box 9:6)
    - Road leading W from new ice house (Box 9:6)
    - Harbor building from E (Box 9:6)
    - Lake front from W end of camp (Box 9:6)
    - Camp group, 2d session (Box 9:6)
    - New ice house from W during construction (Box 9:6)
    - New office building (Box 9:6)
    - State St. looking E from point near harbor (Box 9:6)
    - Road ascending hill near harbor (Box 9:6)
  - 1923 Session
    - Sawing fire wood for Club House (Box 6.9)
    - Center of camp showing mess in background and shop in foreground, 2 plates (Box 6.9)
      [73-74]
    - Big Elm on the shore of Douglas Lake 3/4 mile W of Grapevine Point (Box 6.9)
    - View of camp from hillside above mess (Box 6.9)
      [76]
    - Fireplace in Club House (Box 6.9)
      [78]
    - State St. looking E from center of camp (Box 6.9)
      [79]
    - Big Elm (Box 6.9)
  - 1924 Session
    - Excavating new well (Box 9:6)
    - Camp Davis from the W shore of South Fishtail Bay, 2 plates (Box 9:6)
      [2-3]
    - Part of the staff-Prof. C.O. Carey, Prof. C.T. Johnston, Prof. T.J. Mitchell, Edward Young, Prof. Hugh Brodie, Prof. Harry Bouchard (Box 9:6)
    - Interior of Camp Davis Club, 2 plates (Box 9:6)
      [19-20]
    - Camp Davis looking westerly from shore of Douglas Lake (Box 9:6)
    - Work on new wall (Box 9:6)
    - Camp Davis looking SE from W shore of South Fishtail Bay, 2 plates (Box 9:6)
    - Keeper's house looking NE from point near kitchen (Box 9:6)
      [28]
    - Keeper's residence looking SE from point near store. The projecting wing near the electric light pole is all new construction. The basement part of this wing houses the new well, engine, dynamo, and switchboard (Box 9:6)
    - Interior of work shop (Box 9:6)
    - Interior of work shop (Box 9:7)
  - 1925 Session
    - View of center of camp looking SE, Administration Building in foreground (Box 9:7)
    - Looking E along State St. from point near oak tree, near middle of street, nearly opposite Building 13 (Box 9:7)
    - State St. looking W from point near oak tree, W part of camp (Box 9:7)
    - Looking SW from State St. near middle of camp showing Administration Bldg. in foreground and keeper's house and the mess beyond (Box 9:7)
    - Looking E along State St. from point near center of camp (Box 9:7)
    - Looking W along State St. from point about 200 ft. E of center of camp (Box 9:7)
    - Camp groups, 4 plates (Box 9:7)
      [73-76]
    - Walls of Entrance channel, Camp Davis Harbor (Box 9:7)
    - Building 9 and pavilion (Box 9:7)
      [73]
    - Shore of Douglas Lake, W end of camp and along W side of South Fishtail Bay (Box 9:7)
    - Shore of Douglas Lake in front of camp viewed from point near harbor (Box 9:7)
    - Camp touring car and Michigan Union (Box 9:7)
    - Shore of Douglas Lake at Camp Davis viewed from point just E of harbor (Box 9:7)
      [82]
    - State St. viewed from a point about 200 ft. E of center of camp, looking E (Box 9:7)
    - Shore of Douglas Lake looking W from a point almost in front of Building 13 (Box 9:7)
    - Entrance channel walls, Camp Davis Harbor (Box 9:7)
      [85]
    - Group at Beaver Dam on Carp Creek-Mr. and Mrs. Bishop, Mr. and Mrs. F.D. Johnston, Mr. C.T. Johnston (Box 9:7)
    - View looking NW from point near oak tree toward W end of camp (Box 9:7)
      [87]
    - Looking W along base of hill back of visitors' buildings W of camp (Box 9:7)
      [88]
    - Looking E along S side of State St. from point near Doctor's Building (Box 9:7)
      [89]
    - Looking E along road N of mess (Box 9:7)
      [90]
    - Looking W along road N of mess (Box 9:7)
    - Shore of Douglas Lake in front of camp viewed from a point just W of harbor entrance channel (Box 9:7)
    - Beaver Dam on Carp Creek [93) (Box 9:7)
    - View of center of camp, looking S (Box 9:7)
    - Beaver Dam on Carp Creek (Box 9:7)
    - Night picture showing harbor entrance channel, lake shore and Grapevine Point. Exposure 1/2 hour after dark (Box 9:7)
      [96]
    - Beaver Dam on Carp Creek (Box 9:7)
      [97]
  - 1926 Session
    - Camp groups, 2 plates (Box 9:7)
    - Visitors at Camp Davis prior to opening of session., 2 plates (Box 9:7)
      [29-30]
      (Mr. and Mrs. Franklin D. Johnston, Mr. and Mrs. Clarence T. Johnston in center, Mr. and Mrs. Clarence N. Johnston on right end)
    - Beaver Dam (Box 9:7)
    - Interior of Camp Davis Club showing library (Box 9:7)
    - New garage, showing W and S sides of building, looking E (Box 9:7)
    - Laying floor in new garage, 2 plates (Box 9:7)
      [34-35]
    - Douglas Lake from hilltop of Camp Davis looking N (Box 9:7)
      [37]
    - Camp Davis from W shore of South Fishtail Bay, looking S (Box 9:7)
    - Librarian W.W. Bishop, Mrs. Bishop and William Bishop in boat, Douglas Lake (Box 9:7)
    - N end of new garage (Box 9:7)
    - Harbor entrance channel (Box 9:7)
    - Shore of Douglas Lake at Camp Davis, looking E from point W of harbor (Box 9:7)
    - Keeper's house looking slightly W of N, from hillside just above house (Box 9:7)
    - Camp Davis from W shore of South Fishtail Say (Box 9:7)
    - Laying concrete floor in new garage [451 (Box 9:7)
    - Camp Davis from W shore of South Fishtail Bay, 3 plates (Box 9:7)
      [46-47, 49]
    - Mr. W.W. Bishop and his son William leaving harbor entrance in a boat propelling by outboard motor (Box 9:7)
    - Detailed construction view of new garage to show steel under eaves at gable ends (Box 9:7)
    - New garage with doors on N side open (Box 9:7)
      [53]
    - Trail along W side of Carp Creek (Box 9:7)
    - Interior Harbor Building showing boats put away for the winter (Box 9:7)
      [55]
    - New garage before doors were hung (Box 9:7)
      [56]
    - View along hillside, Camp Davis, looking NW (Box 9:7)
      [57]
  - 1927 Session
    - Looking W along State St. from point near E end of camp (Box 9:7)
    - Tablet erected in memory of the late Prof. Howard S. Merrick. The tablet is placed in the fireplace built by him and in his Building 5 (Box 9:7)
      [45]
    - Part of the shore of N Fishtail Bay looking S (Box 9:7)
    - Fireplace in Prof. Merrick's building and the tablet erected to his memory (Box 9:7)
    - View of State St. looking E from a point near center of camp (Box 9:7)
    - Prof. Merrick's Building S viewed from the lake shore looking S and showing chimney on the N end of the building (Box 9:7)
    - Group near Beaver Dam after end of Summer Session (Box 9:7)
      (back row 1 to rt-Prof. Boston, William Bishop, Mrs. Boston. In front row, Mrs. W.W. Bishop, Mrs. C.T. Johnston, and Mrs. Filibert Roth)
    - View of Beaver Dam and pond back of it taken from E side of Carp Creek (Box 9:7)
    - View of pond back of Beaver Dam looking W (Box 9:7)
    - View of Camp Davis from high ground W of harbor, vertical picture, 2 plates (Box 9:7)
      [54-55]
    - State St. looking W from point near center of camp (Box 9:7)
    - State St. looking W from point near E end of camp (Box 9:7)
    - E shore of North Fishtail Bay. (Box 9:7)
      (This is the only lake shore not owned by the University, from Bryant's E and N, then W to the lands of Dr. Leslie J. French)
    - Camp Davis from boat on Douglas Lake about 1700 ft. to the N, 2 plates (Box 9:7)
      [59-60]
    - Fireplace and tablet in Prof. Merrick's Building 5 (Box 9:7)
      [61]
    - Large elm tree in forest of Jackson and Tindle two or three miles NW of Pellston (Box 9:7)
      [62]
    - Prof. Merrick's Building as viewed from the middle of State St. (Box 9:7)
    - In Jackson and Tindle Forest 2 or 3 miles NW of Pellston (Box 9:7)
    - Entrance channel Camp Davis harbor showing pile of rook as protection against ice (Box 9:7)
    - Fireplace and tablet in Prof. Merrick's Building S (Box 9:7)
    - State St. looking W point opposite Building 13 (Box 9:7)